What do you want us to do?
I would have destroyed all the evidence and everything.
What, what should I do, huh?
Oh, shit, what is there?
Something like that that you can't take or leave out?
Recorded video
That video back then
That's probably it
That's what Hyunwoo Yong instructed.
Don't you remember?
Oh, leave the recording on
Hey, choose quickly, I'll give you 10 seconds.
Oh, wait a minute, wait a minute
- If you don't choose within the time limit
- Ah, wait, wait
Both of them die
I definitely saw the video
There will be a place to store it
It's a video, how do I find it?
You can't search the whole building.
That doesn't mean I'm just going to do it
You can't go in, bro.
On the contrary
Those people are us
How about making it a guide?
Hey, where are you going?
hey!
Woo-sol, are you okay?
Yes, it is possible.
Attach all the cameras like this
Brother, but by any chance
Because of the hidden camera
You're not in prison, are you?
You are just me
You see me as trash?
Oh no, I'm just
'No, right?' Like this
I asked a question, a question
What is that?
What?
Hey, mask
Is it a delivery?
Hyung, but will this be okay?
Yeah, it's a bit, a bit ambiguous.
Security? I think I'll get caught there.
Woosol-ah
You told that kid back then
Did you receive the business card?
yes
Daughter's little brat, s**t, tsk
Are you okay?
If it's Hyunwoo Yong
Won't it pass without a hitch?
'Broadcast room?'
Hey, did we have a broadcasting room too?
Broadcasting room? Hey kid, broadcasting room?
Oh, don't say anything when you write.
I didn't do it
Chairman's game broadcast room
Isn't that what you're talking about?
Because it's something related to the chairman
Put it away well
great job
Hey guys, let's move.
Uh
Wow, this is really working.
Machine room?
Sanghyeop hyung, from now on
I need to draw a map
Oh, oh
No, not right, left.
It's like this
Hey, you loner.
Mr. Chairman, why is the delivery coming to your room?
- What is this?
- I don't know, Mr. Lee, take good care of it.
Hey, clean it up
Dirty bastard, really
Hey, I cleaned it up
What is this?
Should I open it slightly?
Oh, what a surprise, sir
Wow, that's a surprise, really, shit
- uh...
- There's also a map
When you enter the building
I think you'll find plenty
Okay, let's go then.
Should we start now?
Please take care of me, Jeokto-ma
Huh?
What?
Sir, I
Hey, hey!
B4F, Zone B
Check the red truck, now!
Yes, yes, I understand.
- Check everything.
- Yes
I see
What are you hearing?
Sir, there is no one here.
go!
Find out what kind of kid he is now
Bring it before my eyes
If I don't find it, I'll die
Go down and find everything
seed...
Was it you guys' doing?
Even though I lured you, there's still a lot left
How many people? Two, four, six, eight.
I can't even count them now
Go according to plan
Let's split up into teams since there are a lot of opponents.
Woosol and Sanghyeop are on the same team
Yeonjin and I are on the same team
Ugh
One person only cares about his body
The other one only cares about George
The key is to act quickly
Mr. Lee
Ugh! Ugh
Let's go to the next step
I'll find the video evidence.
Are you okay?
Mr. Lee
Let's go!
Go fast, go fast, run, run!
Hey, hey, it's over there.
Wow, over here!
Seongyong hyung
Lee
Mr. Lee
The door opens.
Eww
Where are the recorded video files?
Uh, what, pa, file? No, no.
Tell me quickly before you get hurt.
I see
You crazy bitch, do you want to die?
Ugh
Open everything you have, quickly.
Oh, no, I, I don't know either...
The door opens.
August 22nd, August 22nd
I see
Hey, Mr. Lee
How is it?
I'm beyond my expectations
Let's go down and take a look
Seongyong hyung, are you okay?
are you okay?
Did you find it?
I see
Don't do that
Don't do it
Oh, Wonjun hyung
I really don't know
What should I do
Are you looking for this?
I was really wrong.
I think I lost my mind for a moment
Please don't do that
My friends did nothing wrong
What should I do, Wonjun hyung?
What should I do, I really don't know...
I really really don't know
Oh, Wonjun hyung
I really don't know
What should I do
Uh, uh, no, don't do that
Don't do it, don't do it!
Oh, don't do it, don't do it!
Now that you see it
Are you good at catching cameras?
If you want the video, you should have it.
Send it up
no
You guys don't have that
I'll be back
Take all the kids
Organize the underground parking lot
Yes, I understand.
Let me ask you one thing
Who is the bastard who stabbed Lee Won-jun with a knife?
Right
what?
Are you that little pig?
It's your sister, you fucking bitch.
It's obvious at first glance that I'm your opponent, right?
Hey, knife marks
Want to fight?
Hey!
Come quickly
Chawoosol
Is it hot?
Should I lower the temperature here?
Have you eaten?
Hey, lighten up a bit.
You make me feel
I uploaded it like this
Boy, I'm bored
You are too serious
This is a video file
Take this with you
Or just have some serious fun with me
Select
I'm giving you a chance
A chance for you to take revenge yourself
Who will be next?
Choices come with a price.
Oh, more than a friend
Is family more stimulating?
What is the reason for this?
'reason?'
It's fun